Finding Aid for the Kelly Miller Smith Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- MISCELLANEOUS
  - Prince George County Hospital (Box 143, Folder 25)
  - Report of the Task Force, Salem Baptist Church of Jenkintown, May 21, 1973 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Sears, Roebuck and Co. v. Federal Government, undated (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Sheet Music (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - South and Southern Africa (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Statement of Twenty Black Presbyterians, June 15, 1971 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Surrender of General Lee (Poster) (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Television Viewer Guides (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Tennessee State University - University of Tennessee - Nashville Merger, November 27, 1978 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - University of Washington, 1969 - 1973 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Your Arm's Too Short to Box with God (Box 144, Folder 10)
- WRITINGS BY OTHERS
  - Bankhead, Augustine A., "Our Unreached Potential,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Bermel, Albert, "Miscegenation,", 1963 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Gandy, Ella L., "Blowing in the Wind,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - _, "By What Power?", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - _, "A Call for the Record,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - _, "Carry God on Your Back,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - _, "Clouds But No Rain,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - _, "Come and Behold Them,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - _, "Crisis of Trust,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - _, "The Critical Questions,", undated (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - _, "The Discipline of Change,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - _, "The Family in a World on Fire,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - _, "For the Sake of God,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - _, "From Bethlehem to Nashville with Love,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Gandy, Ella L., "The Glorious King,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "God's Troublemaker: Assault on the System,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "Good Religion and Evil Times,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "Hearing God's Voice Today,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "Let Earth Receive Her King,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "The Living of These Days,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "The Lord Reigneth,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "The Modern Road to Jericho,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "The Morality of Anger,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "Music in a World Aflame,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "Now is the Time,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "The Other Side of Disappointment,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - _, "Our Basic Hunger,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Gandy, Ella L., "Our God in Able,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "Our Spirit-Level Selves,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "The Recovery of Hope,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "Requiem for the Church,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "The Secret of Hope,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "The Silent Majority,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "Such as I Have,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "The Testimony of Experience,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "Triumph of the Skies,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "Urgency of Spiritual Renewal,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "The Voice of Blood,", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "What is this Madness?", 1969 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "Will the Real God Please Stand?", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - _, "The Year of the Lord's Favor,", 1970 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - Hawkins, David, "On Living in Trees,", 1964 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Hughes, Langston, "Thorns,", 1963 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Leonard, Walter J., "The Search for Equality, Roberts v. City of Boston to Bakke v. Regents of the University of California,", 1977 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, C. S., "Onward Christian Spacemen,", 1963 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Moore, William, Jr., "Educational Plight of Blacks in America,", undated (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Moss, Otis, Jr., "A Tribute to Ambassador Andrew Young,", undated (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Robinson, W. R., "The Black Preacher,", 1977 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Rooks, Charles Shelby, "Toward the Promised Land,", 1972 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Taylor, Henry L., "A Challenge to Farmers,", 1960 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - _, "In this Building,", 1959 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - _, "Leadership for Culture and Service,", 1961 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Walton, Hanes, Jr., "Black Politics in the Eighties: A Projective Policy Analysis,", undated (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Williams, Ella Clarke, "An Estimate of Dr. William Herbert Brewster,", undated (Box 145, Folder 2)
- PUBLICATIONS
  - A.M.E. Zion Quarterly Review, 1980 - 1981 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - American Indian Civil Rights Handbook, 1972 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Black Americans, 1969 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Black Child Journal, 1980 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Black Church, 1974 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Black Collegian, 1983, undated (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Black Communicator, 1971 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Black Community Development, by William M. Harris, 1977 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Black Enterprise, 1977 - 1983 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Black Nursing Pioneers, Leaders and Organizers, 1980 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Black Scholar, 1979 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Black Theatre, 1970 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Black and White America, 1969 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Boule Journal, 1978 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Broadcaster, 1960 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Building a Better Sunday School, 1950 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Caribbean Journal of Religious Studies, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Center Magazine, 1971 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Centers of Vigilance, 1977 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Challenge of the Ages, by Frederick Alfred Aston, 1970 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Theological Seminary Register, 1983 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Christian Century, 1962 - 1970 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Christian Century, 1974 - 1979 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Christian Century, 1980 - 1981 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - Christian Century, January - August 1983 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Christian Century, October - December 1983 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Christian Century, January - February 1984 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Christian Century, March - April 1984 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Christian Century, May - June 1984 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Christian Ministry, 1977 - 1984 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Christianity and Crisis, 1969 - 1983 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Christianity Today, 1965 - 1984 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Church Management, 1964 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Civil Liberties, 1969 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Civil Rights Digest, 1972 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Clergy Journal, 1980 - 1984 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Congo Mission News, 1969 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Consumer Reports, 1984 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - The Crisis, 1972 - 1983 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Criterion, 1969 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Current, 1961 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Ebony, 1959 - 1984 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - ECC News, 1980 - 1984 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Economy of Metropolitan Nashville, Tennessee, 1963 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Ecumenical Trends, 1978 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Effective Teaching and School Desegregation, 1965 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Encore, 1975 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Engage/Social Action, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Expository Times, 1972 - 1977 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Events at Orangebur, 1968 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Fambli, 1971 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Family Guide Emergency Health Care, 1970 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Fact Sheets, nos. 106 - 116, 1979 - 1980 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Fisk News, 1967 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Freedomways, 1978 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Freeing the Spirit, 1979 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Futurist, 1977 - 1978 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Friends Journal, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - A Girl and Her Journal, 1955 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - The Good Shepard, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - The Gospels and Christian Ethics, 1960 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Greek Myths, undated (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Harpers, 1971 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Harvard Educational Review, 1967 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Harvard Divinity Bulletin, 1980 - 1981 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Harvard Magazine, 1977 - 1984 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Home Missions, 1968 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Home Missions Notebook, 1978, undated (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Howard University Alumni News, 1979 - 1981 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Howard University Magazine, 1965 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Human Behavior, 1976 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Informer, 1984 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Jet, 1969 - 1983 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Journal of Afro-American Issues, 1977 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Journal of Current Social Issues, 1972 - 1974 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Journal of Interdenominational Theological Center, 1973 - 1975 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Journal of Religious Education, 1967 - 1968 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Journal of Religious Thought, 1945 - 1946 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Journal of Religious Thought, 1947 - 1948 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Journal of Religious Thought, 1949 - 1950 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Journal of Religious Thought, 1959 - 1964 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Journal of Religious Thought, 1967 - 1969 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Journal of Religious Thought, 1970 - 1974 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Katallagete, 1970 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Koinonia, 1969 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Kudzu Vine, 1978 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Liberation and Unity, 1973 Liberty, 1965 - 1984 Look, 1961 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Meredith, 1982 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Message, 1982 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - A Minister's Involvement in the Racial Crisis, 1959 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Ministry, 1978 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Ministry, 1979 - 1982 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Nashville, 1979 - 1984 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Nation, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - National Leader, 1982 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - The Negro at Nashville, 1913 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - New Book Review, 1974 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - New Directions, 1981 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - New South, 1960 - 1963 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - One World, 1978 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Peabody Journal of Education, 1978 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - People in the News, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Perspectives for a Study of Afro-American Religions in the U.S., 1971 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, 1977 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Pride, 1971 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Psychology Today, 1967 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Pulpit Digest (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Quarterly Review, 1980 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - The Record of President Carter's Administration, 1979 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Role of the White Liberals in Changing Patterns and Race Relations in the South, 1962 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Rhythm, 1970 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Sechaba, 1969 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - The Seven Virtues of Mahatma Gandhi, 1978 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Sojourners, 1977 - 1980 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Sojourners, 1983 - 1984 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - South Today, 1969 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Southern Africa, 1980 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Southern Exposure, undated (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Sports Illustrated, 1984 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Stepping Stones to Freedom, 1960 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Story of My Life and Work by Elnora D. McGowan, 1966 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - TAB, 1980 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - The Taborian, 1959 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Taborian Bulletin, 1959 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Tell It Like It Is, 1968 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Theological Education, 1970 - 1971 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Through the Year With World Book, 1958 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Time, 1963 - 1977 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Today's Education, 1976 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Twelve Hundred Questions, 1958 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Twenty Centuries of Jewish Life in the Holy Land, 1976 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Urban West, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Vine Life, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - What Is the Death of God Theology, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - When Motivated and Trained Church Workers Respond and Gladly Serve, 1949 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Who's Who Among the American Black Churches, 1978 - 1979 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Will Women Ever Respect Men?, 1981 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Witness, 1979 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Worker, 1974 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - World Parish, 1980 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Your Church, 1976 - 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
- NOTES
  - Abortion and the Christian..., undated (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Charles, March 22, 1979 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action, undated (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Agenda for the 80's, undated (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Arradondo, November 9, 1978 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Authority Meets Power, undated (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Ballinger, Richard, undated (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Bible Use, undated (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Biblical Perspective, undated (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Billingsley, Andrew, November 9, 1972 (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Black, H. D., undated (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Black Church and Contemporary Social Problems, September 2, 1974 -December 6, 1976 (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - Black Church As Economic Agency, undated (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - Black Church in America, September 16, 1975 - December 7, 1982, undated (Box 155, Folder 14)
  - The Black Church in Nashville: Profile and Prospects, October 15, 1976 (Box 155, Folder 15)
  - The Black Church: Our Heritage, Our Hope, undated (Box 155, Folder 16)
  - Black Clergy and Social Issues, September 20, 1976 - December 3, 1982, undated (Box 155, Folder 17)
  - Black Extremism — Justifies Sin?, undated (Box 155, Folder 18)
  - Black Morality and the Black Church, undated (Box 155, Folder 19)
  - Black Pastor in the U.S.A., February 24, 1977 - November 25, 1981 (Box 155, Folder 20)
  - Black Power Clergy, undated (Box 155, Folder 21)
  - Black Preachers/Preaching, undated (Box 155, Folder 22)
  - Black Religion and Black Politics, March 6, 1973 (Box 155, Folder 23)
  - Black Religious Experience, December 7, 1970, undated (Box 155, Folder 24)
  - Black Religious Leadership, February 17, 1976 - March 23, 1983 (Box 155, Folder 25)
  - Board of Education, October 6, 1970 (Box 155, Folder 26)
  - Bottom Line, undated (Box 155, Folder 27)
  - Celebrate Christ's Church, undated (Box 155, Folder 28)
  - Characteristics of Black Nationalism, undated (Box 155, Folder 29)
  - Chart, 1961 (Box 155, Folder 30)
  - Chip Murray: Pray Together, Children! No. 21, October 29, 1980 (Box 155, Folder 31)
  - Christian Doctrines, undated (Box 155, Folder 32)
  - Christian Education and the Black Church: A Contextual Approach, undated (Box 155, Folder 33)
  - Chronology in Violence, undated (Box 155, Folder 34)
  - Church Organizations Formed During Present and Pastoral Administration, undated (Box 155, Folder 35)
  - Clift, Arlene, October 4, 1982 (Box 155, Folder 36)
  - Committed to Witness, undated (Box 155, Folder 37)
  - Crawford, Evans, undated (Box 155, Folder 38)
  - Cry for the Children, undated (Box 155, Folder 39)
  - Cry from the Streets, undated (Box 155, Folder 40)
  - Cry Why?, undated (Box 155, Folder 41)
  - Dare We Thank god for the Church Even Today?, undated (Box 155, Folder 42)
  - Dennis, Ruth, April 10, 1979 (Box 155, Folder 43)
  - Digest of Sermon, "Perspectives on Human Need," undated (Box 155, Folder 44)
  - Disappointed, undated (Box 155, Folder 45)
  - Divine Design and Human Disorder, undated (Box 155, Folder 46)
  - Divorce Project, September 22, 1977 (Box 155, Folder 47)
  - Dodson, "Strategies for Liberation,", undated (Box 155, Folder 48)
  - The Early Period, undated (Box 155, Folder 49)
  - Elam, Lloyd, March 11, 1976 - November 30, 1978, undated (Box 155, Folder 50)
  - Ewing, Russell, C. B., undated (Box 155, Folder 51)
  - Faculty Retreat, September 24 - 25, 1982 (Box 155, Folder 52)
  - Financial Impact of Death on the Black, undated (Box 155, Folder 53)
  - Foundation Stones for Viable Church Education, undated (Box 155, Folder 54)
  - General Observations (re: Black Universities), undated (Box 155, Folder 55)
  - Gist of Program of Work, undated (Box 155, Folder 56)
  - Hamilton, Charles, February 15, 1979 (Box 155, Folder 57)
  - Haney, James, undated (Box 155, Folder 58)
  - Health and Financial Problems Lecture Series, 5, 1981 (Box 155, Folder 59)
  - The Hope that is Within Me, undated (Box 155, Folder 60)
  - Housing and Urban Development Department, undated (Box 155, Folder 61)
  - How to Leave Babylon, undated (Box 155, Folder 62)
  - How to Read and Study the Bible, undated (Box 155, Folder 63)
  - Identifying the "Lost,", undated (Box 155, Folder 64)
  - Influences on Martin Luther King's Thoughts, undated (Box 155, Folder 65)
  - The Informed Witness, undated (Box 155, Folder 66)
  - Inner City Church Must Be A Church, undated (Box 155, Folder 67)
  - Interpretation of Purpose, undated (Box 155, Folder 68)
  - Jesus and the Spiritually Delinquent, undated (Box 155, Folder 69)
  - Jones, Amos, November 6, 1979 (Box 155, Folder 70)
  - Jones, Levi, September 22, 1977 (Box 155, Folder 71)
  - Junior, Samella, September 28, 1978 (Box 155, Folder 72)
  - Legacy of Love, in Memoriam Martin Luther King, Sr., undated (Box 155, Folder 73)
  - The Life of Hope in Us, undated (Box 155, Folder 74)
  - Life's Conditional Guide, undated (Box 155, Folder 75)
  - Lift Every Voice, undated (Box 155, Folder 76)
  - Light Upon the Mountain, undated (Box 155, Folder 77)
  - Locating the Good News During Unique Crises, undated (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - The McKinney Report, undated (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - McDaniel, Paul, November 5, 1977 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Management of Black Church People, undated (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Marbury, Carl, July 19, 1971 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Mono-Dialogue, undated (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Music and Task of Liberation, undated (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Narrator and Metaphor in Biblical Writing, undated (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Obedience, undated (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Old Testament, undated (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - On Not Keeping the Peace, undated (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - On Being Aware, undated (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - On Being Less than God, undated (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - Organizing Principle of Christian's Life, undated (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - Paris, Peter, November 3, 1974 - February 8, 1979 (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - The Problem of Black Oppression in Nashville, November 15, 1971 (Box 156, Folder 16)
  - Proclamation Involves, undated (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - Racism as the Primary Contemporary Social Problem, October 7, 1974 (Box 156, Folder 18)
  - Reaching Out, 1982 (Box 156, Folder 19)
  - Reflections on Fauntroy, April 20, 1978 (Box 156, Folder 20)
  - Religion and Society in the Black Experience, October 27, 1977 - March 29, 1979 (Box 156, Folder 21)
  - Religions of Black Americans and the Black Muslims in the U.S.A., March 7, 1972 (Box 156, Folder 22)
  - Requisites for Ministry, 1978 (Box 156, Folder 23)
  - Resolution on Human Rights, undated (Box 156, Folder 24)
  - Roberts, J. DeOtis, March 27, 1979 (Box 156, Folder 25)
  - St. Louis Workshop on Cooperation, 1981 (Box 156, Folder 26)
  - Sermon, January 4, 1982 (Box 156, Folder 27)
  - Setting of Church in Africa, undated (Box 156, Folder 28)
  - The Silence of Death, undated (Box 156, Folder 29)
  - Slave Worship and African Survivals, undated (Box 156, Folder 30)
  - Social Changes, undated (Box 156, Folder 31)
  - Somalia, undated (Box 156, Folder 32)
  - Some issues Involved in Black Death, undated (Box 156, Folder 33)
  - "Soul" Refers to the Authentic Self, undated (Box 156, Folder 34)
  - Special Meeting with Hubbard Hospital, December 13, 1980 (Box 156, Folder 35)
  - Dr. Spence Conference, February 2, 1981 (Box 156, Folder 36)
  - Steele, Charles Bradford, undated (Box 156, Folder 37)
  - Stevenson, Adlai, undated (Box 156, Folder 38)
  - Stone, Sonja, October 7, 1980, undated (Box 156, Folder 39)
  - Student Notebooks, 1942 - 1944, undated (Box 156, Folder 40)
  - Sydnor, III, Rev. Alvin, undated (Box 156, Folder 41)
  - Things to Do Today, June 7, 1983 (Box 156, Folder 42)
  - Things to Do Tonight, December 22, 1969 (Box 156, Folder 43)
  - Thurman, Howard, undated (Box 156, Folder 44)
  - Topics for Further Research, undated (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Topics for Study, undated (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Understanding the Task and Challenge of Evangelism, undated (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Vanderbilt Divinity School, January 8, 1979 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Watergate Backwards, undated (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Webb, Lillian, February 12, 1980 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Webster, Sherman, September 23, 1974 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - What Blacks Have at Stake, undated (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Where Are We?, undated (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Whither Shall I Flee?, undated (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Youth Seeks an Abundant Life, undated (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Unidentified (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Fragments (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Fragments (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Fragments (Box 157, Folder 15)
- VU / VDS Files (Alphabetically)
  - Academy of the Church in Transition (Box 157, Folder 16)
  - Black Faculty Appointment Committee (Box 157, Folder 17)
  - Black Faculty Association (Box 157, Folder 18)
  - Black Studies Committee (Box 157, Folder 19)
  - Black Studies Committee (Box 157, Folder 20)
  - Black Studies Committee (Box 157, Folder 21)
  - Black Studies Committee (Box 157, Folder 22)
  - Black Theological Education in the U.S. (Proposal) (Box 157, Folder 23)
  - Chapel and Convocation (Box 157, Folder 24)
  - Church, Ministry and Community (Box 157, Folder 25)
  - Cole Lectures '76 (Box 157, Folder 26)
  - Conference on Black Church Management (Box 157, Folder 27)
  - Conference on Black Women and the Church (General Information and Expense Reports) (Box 157, Folder 28)
  - Conference on Black Women and the Church (General Information; Committee Planning Reports; Draft of Transcribed Keynote Address) (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Conference on Black Women and the Church (Registration) (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Conference on Black Women and the Church (Clippings) (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Conference on the Church and the Black Elderly, November 12 - 13, 1974 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Consultation on the Black Church in Community Economic Development (Proposal) (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Consultation on the Black Church in Community Economic Development (Related Items) (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Continuing Education and Special Programs (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Doctor of Ministry Studies (VDS) (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School Degrees in Religion (VU) (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School Degrees in Religion (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Theological Union (Berkeley, CA) (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Humanities Project — VDS (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Joint University Libraries (JUL) (1969 - 1972) (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Joint University Libraries (JUL) (1974 - 1976) (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - Proposal — Education for Practicing Black Ministers (Box 158, Folder 15)
  - Prospectus (VDS Publication) (1973 - 1974) (Box 158, Folder 16)
  - Prospectus (VDS Publication) (1975 - 1980) (Box 158, Folder 17)
  - Search for a New Dean (VDS) (Box 158, Folder 18)
  - Spire (VDS Publication) (Box 158, Folder 18)
  - Sponsored Research Notes (1972) (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Sponsored Research Notes (1973) (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Sponsored Research Notes (1974) (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Sponsored Research Notes (1975) (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Vanderbilt University — Clippings (Box 159, Folder 5)
- MISCELLANEOUS OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Tennessee State Plan for Comprehensive Mental Health Services, 1976 (Box 159, Folder 6)